kngine.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy - Kngine

**Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services.  
Kngine.com does not rent, sell, or share information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies. In general, we only use the collected information for provide and improve our services. When you conduct a search on Kngine.com, we use the search terms you submit along with the information set forth above to provide you with relevant search results.   

**Log Data**

When you visit Kngine.com, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to Kngine.com, pages of Kngine.com that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on Kngine.com, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of Kngine.com and for the technical administration, and to improve our service.

**Cookies**

We currentily don't use “cookies”. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to and collected information to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the collected information.

**Agreement and Changes**

By using the Services, you agree to the current Privacy Policy. Kngine reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, discontinue, or terminate the Services or to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Contact Us**

If you have any question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at[ Info@Kngine.com](mailto:Info@Kngine.com)
